(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
BAU BAU!
いっくよー！
Let's go!
BAU BAU BAU!
FUWAMOCO!
Waffy!
It's showtime! 一緒にいたいよ
It's showtime! I want to be with you
Lifetime showtime anytime BAU BAU BAU yeah
Future is bright
Fluffy fuzzy yappy sisters!
Lifetime showtime
FUWA! MOCO!
BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU BAU
My heart 'n' soul 'n' tail are FUWAWA (Yeah!)
I'm so fluffy that even I could float away
Just call for me, we're only a bark away
Your smile is the treasure that I wanna keep safe
FUWA! MOCO!
I love being tricky. Doggy kisses are for me.
I love lots of walkies. Don't need no leashes for me.
Silly puppy Mococo will follow you anywhere
FUWAMOCO together, take us along with you
Barking oh so merrily!
It's showtime! 一緒にいたいよ (Oh!)
It's showtime! I want to be with you (Oh!)
Lifetime showtime anytime BAU BAU BAU
一生涯 sing with you
Sing with you for a lifetime
Stars wink moon spotlight furr-over glow
It's showtime! 一緒にいたいよ
It's showtime! I want to be with you
Lifetime showtime anytime BAU BAU BAU yeah
Future is bright
Fluffy fuzzy yappy sisters!
Woooooo... BAU!
Woooooo...
Way back then, all locked up we were stuck in the cell
Holding back, doggy dog kept sealed away (BAU!)
Bouta burst, fluff & fuzz we're meant to be free
Moko
Bouta burst, fluff & fuzz,
we're meant to be free
Make a break for it, it's playtime!
Paws hitting the pavement
Dreams sparklin' within our eyes
Gonna keep you smilin'
My sneezes won't stop flyin' by
Even though we're still just a pair
of scaredy puppy dogs
The bond that we share as twins is irreplaceable
We're a pair unbreakable!
And that's why
いつだって
No matter when
It's that day!
Today!
Lifetime! Showtime! Not tomorrow!
BAU BAU!
一生涯
For a lifetime,
Walk with you!
Good times and bad times, it doesn't matter!
いつだって
No matter when
It's that day!
Lifetime! Showtime! Everyday!
BAU BAU!
Yeah,
二人は
The two of us are
Happy Lucky Puppy Sisters!
FUWAMOCO BAU BAU! Everybody MOKO!
Hallo hallo BAU BAU! Everybody BAU!
ダメダメノンノン
No no non non
Don't touch the ears!
モフモフノンノン
Floof floof non non
Don't touch the tail!
チワワじゃないよ
I'm not a chihuahua
フワワだよ
I'm Fuwawa
BAU!
フワワじゃないよ
I'm not Fuwawa
モココだよ
I'm Mococo
BAU!
Twin demon guard dog sisters, yeah! BAU!
And together we're... FUWAMOCO!
Gather up our dreams
And suddenly you'll come to realize
There's as many as there are stars
Illuminating the night sky
Never-ending dreams
We don't know if they all can be achieved
But we'll keep on going furr-ever
Together here with you!
It's showtime!
一緒にいたい！ Whoo-hoo!
I want to be with you! Whoo-hoo!
It's showtime!
一緒にいたい！ Whoo-hoo!
I want to be with you! Whoo-hoo!
It's showtime!
一緒にいたいよ
I want to be together!
Fuwa fuwa
Moco moco
Hand in hand with you!
Bring your smile,
rain or shine,
We'll protect it
won't forget our
pledge to you!
It's showtime!
一緒にいたい！
I want to be with you!
Oh!
Lifetime Showtime! Anytime!
BAU BAU!
一生涯
For a lifetime,
Sing with you!
Stars wink,
moon spotlight,
furr-ever glow!
It's showtime!
一緒にいたいよ
I want to be together!
Lifetime Showtime! Anytime!
BAU BAU!
And
Together
We're
Happy Fuzzy Puppy Sisters!
Let's hear you! Say it loud!
FUWA!
MOCO!
BAU BAU!
Yeah!
FUWAMOCO BAU BAU!
BAU!
Ruff!
Bau Bau!
Welcome to our
FuwaMoco Wacha Wacha
Birthday Festival!
Ruff!
Bau Bau!
Thank you so much for coming to celebrate
our birthday with us! Ruff!
始まりましたー！
We've started!
今日は生誕ライブに来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you for coming to our birthday live today!
Thank you! Well, to continue off
from yesterday's variety show, tonight again,
today we have a big concert!
Ruff! Can you believe it?
It's already been three years!
Right? Our third birthday
in Hololive with you! Ruff!
Ah, Mococo-chan,
we can't forget that really important thing, right?
Hoi?
Introductions!
Ah, yeah! Okay!
I'm not a chihuahua, I'm Fuwawa!
I'm not Fuwawa, I'm Mococo!
We're Hololive English Advent's
twin demon guard dog sisters!
Together we're FuwaMoco!
Bau Bau!
Ruff! And look!
We have an amazing birthday festival stage here!
Amazing stage! Ruff!
It's so big!
Ruff! It's so big! Ruff!
And it's such a big boost for us too!
Ah, Fuwawa! Can we?
Hoi!
Okay, here we go!
Three, two, one...
Bau Bau!
It's so big and wide!
Ruff! Thank you puppies
for being here today!
Ruff!
But, singing and dancing today
is not just going to be us, right?
No, we're also here
with some very special guests too!
そう、今日はとっても素敵な
Yes, today we have some very lovely
ゲストさんも来てるから、ぜひ楽しみにしててね！
guests coming, so please look forward to it!
そして、え？
And, wait?
もう一人謎のゲストさんも？
Another mysterious guest too?
誰かなー？
I wonder who it is?
Ruff!
Bau Bau!
Ruff! But, a birthday
wouldn't be complete without this, right?
Right! Something very important.
I think you know well, but...
Ah...
Hashtag!
Yes, the birthday hashtag!
Right up here, you can see our birthday hashtag.
Hashtag FWMC B-day 26 (#FWMCbday26).
That it is!
Ruff! Please, please
post your thoughts, take lots of photos,
screenshots...
ぜひハッシュタグで感想呟いてください。
Please tweet your thoughts with the hashtag.
写真もね、後でポチしに行くからね。
I'll go and 'like' your photos later too.
Ruff! Mococo will check out
all your thoughts after the show, so...
Ruff!
Bau Bau!
Woah!
Also!
We're going to be having a special membership only concert right after this!
So don't miss it, okay?
Yeah! Uh-huh!
最後にはメン限のアンコールライブもありますので、ぜひ見に来てくださいね！
Lastly, there will also be a membership-only encore live, so please come and see it!
Bau bau!
Woah!
Uh!
You know, it is a concert after all, right? So we should get singing a little more, yeah?
Yeah, yeah! Uh-huh!
Woah!
Oh!
For this next song, I think we need a special guest, right?
Yeah, uh-huh! Okay!
Let's call her on together!
Okay! Haha!
Calli-senpai!!
Hey hey hey hey hey hey!
皆さん！
Everyone!
Bau bau!!
Today only, I am also a dog.
Bau bau bau bau!
Shinigami dog!
Yeah!
Happy birthday, FUWAMOCO! Bau bau!
Thank you for inviting me, I'm happy to be here.
What's up, Ruffians?
Yeah!
But I see you have a pretty nice shirt there, huh?
I do!
Wow! Look at this logo! What does it say?
Check it out!
With respect! With respect! With respect! With respect! With respect!
But, you know, it'd be cute if we matched, right? Right?
Yeah! Oh! Right!
But maybe, we'll just go run and we'll get changed, and you entertain the Ruffians for a second?
Yeah, okay! Entertain them!
Okay!
You can do it!
I got this.
They won't bite! They won't bite!
Okay, bye bye!
Ruffians, welcome to Mori Calliope super special splits challenge segment!
いくぞ！
Let's go!
I can't... I'm sorry, I can't. I can't do it!
I did my best.
Safe, safe, safe, safe!
Yeah! Uh-huh!
But now...
That's right!
Matching!! Matching!!
Twinning! Tripling! Tripling!
Wow! That's a nice ring to it.
Yeah! Oh!
Um, this next song is one that FUWAMOCO, we wanted to sing with you for such a long time!
Yeah, yeah!
Something nostalgic and I think you'll be able to see why. There's some rap in there as well.
Oh, yeah! Uh-huh! But it's also very cute, right?
Yes!
次歌う曲は、Calli先輩と一緒にはずっと歌いたかった大好きな曲です。
The next song we'll sing is a song I love that I've wanted to sing with Calli-senpai forever.
Yeah! It's both cute, it's cool, yeah! But I think, you know, it shows...
...an important part, that you know, you should be proud of what you like, right?
Important meaning of being proud, being strong about what you like, yeah!
Yeah, your likes.
And whether that be games, anime, idols, figures, or maybe even Vtubers!
Oh, nice choice there.
Yeah, you know, after all, life is more fun when you're just true to yourself, right?
Definitely. Uh-huh! I agree!
So we're going to sing this song for you, okay?
Okay, let's do the title call together, okay?
Yes!
聴いてください！
Please listen!
Like! Like! Like!
Like! Like! Like! My trial behind
Comic, I Like it!
Music, I Like it!
Game, I Like it!
Animation, I Like it!
Figure, I Like it!
Movie, I Like it!
Wonder, I Like it!
Hobby, I Like it!
go go go go go go go go go go go go go go
Do you like it? I like it!
I Like it! do you like it?
人生楽しんだもん勝ち 狙うはサバイバル
Life's a game, so enjoy it; survival is the goal
好きなもの好きって言えたら それ超新星(スーパーノヴァ)
If you can say you love what you love, you're a supernova
快感中枢 即MAX 狙わばサバイバル
Pleasure centers straight to the MAX; survival is the goal
まるで勝ち誇るかのように歌えばド真ん中
Sing as if triumphantly, right in the bullseye
プラスチック、マジック、ロマン、口説くテクは満開、時給は一生でしょ
Plastic, magic, romance, courting skills in full bloom; the pay is for a lifetime
NO迷い、煌めきそうな、今すぐ Let's make sound
No hesitation, seemingly sparkling; right now, Let's make sound
キミがお部屋にいたってリンクすればコンサート
Even if you're in your room, once we link up, it's a concert
いつだって Only lonely only lonely 準備はオーライさ
Always only lonely, only lonely; preparation is all right
I like it! I like it! 好きになれば
I like it! I like it! If you fall in love
きっとすべてがカラフルで
Surely everything will be colorful
Lucky! Lucky! 星屑さえ
Lucky! Lucky! Even the stardust
光る宝物さ
Will be a shining treasure
I like it! I like it! キミに会えた
I like it! I like it! I met you
やっと今日からよろしくね
Finally, from today on, nice to meet you
ホラ、キラキラ 夢みたい
Look, sparkling, it's like a dream
早く抱きしめたい
I want to hug you right away
アレもコレも欲しくて
I want that and this too
神様に祈ってる
I'm praying to God
...ねえ 好きでしょ
...Hey, you like it, right?
しょうがない
It can't be helped
次はなににしようかな
What should I do next?
歩く終わらない トビ回るは四つ星 言葉 Like Like yeah
Walking without end, spinning around four stars, words Like Like yeah
360度パノラマ全方向 大好きの陣
360-degree panorama in all directions, the formation of love
何か一つでもいいから のめり込める自分のアイテム
Even just one thing is fine, a thing of your own to get lost in
Like a Super Star Firemen 無敵キャンディ 他、代替来世
Like a Super Star Firemen, invincible candy, others are for the next life
望んでる彼もきっと 現世がいとおしくなるはずなのさ
The person you're wishing for will surely find this life precious too
成ろうとして成るもんじゃない 人生楽しんで歩こうじゃない
It's not something you become by trying; why not enjoy life as you walk?
自分に素直であれ スポットライト僕らを照らせ
Be true to yourself, let the spotlight shine on us
今日も愛を叫ぶだけだ Get up!
Today, I'll just shout my love, Get up!
捧げたい Song for you!
The song I want to dedicate to you!
I Like It! I Like It!
手を伸ばせば きっと全てがミラクルで
If you reach out, everything will surely be a miracle
Happy! Happy!
日常でさえ 夢の物語さ
Even everyday life is a dream-like story
I Like It! I Like It!
キミに会えた ずっと離さないでいてね
I met you, please never let me go
ほら キラキラ虹みたい 世界はまわりだす
Look, it's like a sparkling rainbow, the world begins to turn
好き、好き、好きでしょう！大勝負
I'll take a gamble with "Like, like, like!"
抱えていたいこの感情
This feeling I want to keep holding
歯止め外すよ真剣勝負
I'm letting go of the brakes, it's a real showdown
ためらわないのがいいんでしょ
It's better not to hesitate, right?
そう、恋をもっと実験
Yes, let's experiment more with love
でもそれが僕の等身大
But that's my true self
キャスト飛ばし世界を革命
Skipping the cast and revolutionizing the world
いわゆる一つの萌え要素
It's what you'd call a "moe" element
素直になれたなら Happy days
If I could be honest, these would be happy days
I Like It! I Like It!
好きになれば きっと全てがカラフルで
If you fall in love, everything will surely be colorful
Lucky! Lucky!
星屑さえ 光る宝物さ
Even the stardust is a shining treasure
I Like It! I Like It!
キミに会えた やっと今日からよろしくね
I met you, finally starting today, please be good to me
ほら キラキラ夢みたい 早く抱きしめたい
Look, it's like a sparkling dream, I want to hold you soon
I Like It! I Like It!
手を伸ばせば きっと全てがミラクルで
If you reach out, everything will surely be a miracle
Happy! Happy!
日常でさえ 夢の物語さ
Even everyday life is a dream-like story
I Like It! I Like It!
キミに会えた ずっと離さないでいてね
I met you, please never let me go
ほら キラキラ虹みたい 世界はまわりだす
Look, it's like a sparkling rainbow, the world begins to turn
Calli-senpai! Yeah!
Oh bau! Oh bau!
Oh bau!
I like FuwaMoco!
I like Calli-senpai!
Bye bye bau bau! Bye bye!
Please listen to our next song.
Jo t'aime, Jo t'aime.
Jo t'aime ★ Jo t'aime / Lyrics: Tommy february6 / Music: MALIBU CONVERTIBLE
街角に並ぶ 映画のポスター
Movie posters lining the street corner
もうこの街にも 飽きたわ
I've grown tired of this city already
終バスの向こうに ため息を返す
Beyond the last bus, I exhale a sigh
キャンセルしないで Mon amour pour toi
Don't cancel, my love for you
ハートのぬけがらに 隠した写真
A photo hidden in the hollow shell of my heart
誰も知らない 本気の恋 神様は気づいてる
A serious love that nobody knows, God has noticed it
Jo t'aime ★ Jo t'aime 叶わない夢なんて 見たくないわ
Jo t'aime ★ Jo t'aime, I don't want to see unfulfillable dreams
でもロマンス 目覚めてゆく
But romance is waking up
“愛してるわ” クレープに描く 愛の傘の下で
"I love you," drawn on a crepe, under the umbrella of love
止まぬ雨の音 Jo t'aime ★ Jo t'aime
The sound of unending rain, Jo t'aime ★ Jo t'aime
こんな不本意な夜に
I don't want to spend
したくはないから
Such a disappointing night,
ほんの5分でも
Even for just
会いたい
Five minutes, I want to see you.
キャンディショップも
The candy shop
レコードショップも
And the record shop,
あなたがいないと　つまらない
They're all boring without you.
ジャケットのポケットに　入れたままのコインに
With the coin left in my jacket pocket,
賭けるわ　恋の行方
I'll bet on the direction of love,
神様が知っている
Only God knows.
Je t'aime ★ Je t'aime
退屈な恋なんてしたくないわ
I don't want a boring love.
あっという間に溺れてく
I'm drowning in an instant.
“今がすべて”
“Now is everything,”
カフェ・オ・レが冷めてしまうその前に
Before the café au lait gets cold,
もう一度KISSして
Kiss me once more,
Je t'aime ★ Je t'aime
物語に鍵をかけて
Locking the story away,
ド・ジュアン・ジュ
Deux jeunes gens,
あなたの言葉ばかりを夢見ている
I'm only dreaming of your words.
Mon Amour　Je t'aime ★ Je t'aime
Mon Amour, Je t'aime ★ Je t'aime,
叶わない夢なんて見たくないわ
I don't want to see unfulfilled dreams.
でもロマンス目覚めてゆく
But romance is waking up.
“愛してるわ”
“I love you,”
クレープに描く愛の傘の下で
Under the umbrella of love drawn on a crepe,
止まぬ雨の音
The sound of endless rain,
Je t'aime ★ Je t'aime
Mon Amour, pour toi
退屈な恋なんてしたくないわ
I don't want a boring love.
あっという間に溺れてく
I'm drowning in an instant.
“今がすべて”
“Now is everything,”
カフェ・オ・レが冷めてしまうその前に
Before the café au lait gets cold,
もう一度聴かせて
Let me hear it once more,
Je t'aime ★ Je t'aime
Bau Bau!
Wow, look at the sunset!
Oh, it's setting already.
Perfect timing!
Well, that last song was "Je t'aime ★ Je t'aime".
What did you think, Mococo?
What'd you think, Ruffians?
It's a little bit more nostalgic.
Yeah, maybe even a bit melancholic of a song.
You know, some city pop vibes too!
Yeah! And the choreography's cute too, right?
Well, we hope it made you feel nice and warm and fluffy, Ruffians!
You know, with the sun setting now,
it's starting to feel a bit romantic almost, right?
Well, I guess it's the perfect time to call out my next guest!
Yeah! Here we go!
AZKi-senpai! Akirose-senpai!
Bau Bau! Welcome!
誕生日おめでとう！
Happy birthday!
Happy birthday! Thank you! Bau Bau!
Thank you so much for coming!
おめでとうー！ふあちゃん、もこちゃん！
Happy birthday, Fuwa-chan, Moco-chan!
Thank you! Please introduce yourselves!
こんこんこんこんあずき！AZKiです！
Ko-ko-ko-ko-zuki! I'm AZKi!
ホロライブ1期生の、異世界からやってきたハーフエルフ、
Hololive 1st generation's half-elf from another world,
アキ・ローゼンタールことアキロゼです！やっほー！バウバウ！
Aki Rosenthal, also known as Akirose! Yahoo! Bau Bau!
Bau Bau! AZKi-senpai, Akirose-senpai,
Thank you so much for coming!
誕生日おめでとうー！
Happy birthday!
このステージ、凄いねー！
This stage is amazing!
Yeah, we really love...
...AZKi-senpai and Akirose-senpai's singing voices, so...
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
We actually have a special song that we want to perform with you!
アキロゼ先輩とあずき先輩はとっても魅力的なお姉さんたちなので...
Aki-rose-senpai and AZKi-senpai are such charming older sisters, so...
あら、あら
Oh my, oh my.
一緒にこの曲で行こうかなと思いました！
I thought we should do this song together!
ちょっとね、日も暮れてますし
The sun is starting to set a bit...
確かにちょっと夕方...
True, it's getting toward evening...
ロマンチックになりましたね
It's become quite romantic, hasn't it?
実はちょっぴりセクシーかも？
Actually, it might even be a little sexy?
セクシーかも！
Maybe sexy!
セクシーな曲？
A sexy song?
お願いしたことがあるみたいなんですけど...
It seems like I have a request for you...
アキロゼ先輩、えっと、この曲を歌う前に少しあの... セクシーなウォーミングアップ...
Aki-rose-senpai, um, before we sing this song, a little... sexy warm-up...
いいですか？いいですか？
Is that okay? Is that okay?
セクシーウォーミングアップ！OK！
Sexy warm-up! OK!
じゃあまずセクシーな体を作るために...
Well then, first, to shape a sexy body...
自分のボディをなでて...
Stroke your own body...
なでて！なでて！頭なでて！足から！足から！
Stroke! Stroke! Stroke your head! From your feet! From your feet!
なでてみて！なでてみて！
Try stroking! Try stroking!
はずい！
Embarrassing!
アキロゼ先輩みたいに！
Like Aki-rose-senpai!
モコちゃん可愛いよ！オッケーいいよ！
Moco-chan is so cute! Okay, good!
なでるのがセクシー。足から、足から。
Stroking is sexy. From the feet, from the feet.
もう一回、もう一回！
One more time, one more time!
あずきちゃんもなんかセクシーだけど可愛い、ちょっと可愛いなと思いました
AZKi-chan is also somehow sexy but cute, I thought she was a bit cute.
やっぱりこうやって...
As expected, like this...
尻尾、尻尾も！尻尾フリフリも！
The tail, the tail too! Wag your tail too!
ウォーミングアップ、ウォーミングアップ！
Warm-up, warm-up!
いいんじゃない、いいんじゃない。オッケーできた！
Isn't it good, isn't it good? Okay, done!
いい感じになりましたね！
It's looking good now!
じゃあ、次の曲行きましょうか！はい！
Then, shall we go to the next song! Yes!
聞いてください。ディスコティーク！
Please listen. DISCOTHEQUE!
チュル チュル チュル パヤパ
Chul chul chul payapa
DISCO BABY DISCO BABY
DISCO MONSTER DISCO MONSTER
DISCOTHEQUE
Lyrics: 園田凌士
Music: 上松範康 (Elements Garden)
DISCOTHEQUE
Lyrics: Ryoji Sonoda
Music: Noriyasu Agematsu (Elements Garden)
SWEETIE DARLIN' 踊りましょう
SWEETIE DARLIN' let's dance
弾ける BEAUTY LADY
The sparkling BEAUTY LADY
生まれ変わって 甘い夢 そっと彩りたいの
I want to be reborn and gently color my sweet dreams
まだらな唇
Mottled lips
ピンク色の艶めくネイル
Glossy pink nails
ガラスの向こう側に映る素顔
My true face reflected on the other side of the glass
シュールだね
Is surreal, isn't it?
君だけにそい見せていたい
I want to stay by your side and show only you
心の中 瞳の奥
Inside my heart, deep in my eyes
そばにいてほしいよ
I want you to be by my side
きらめく波 照らされて
Illuminated by the sparkling waves
MY DARLIN' ねえ ヴィヴィッドな恋しましょう
MY DARLIN' hey, let's have a vivid love
弾ける SEXY BEAUTY
The sparkling SEXY BEAUTY
生まれ変わって 甘い夢 そっと彩る MY LOVE ほら
Reborn, look, my love gently colors my sweet dreams
世界は変わる
The world will change
チュル チュル チュル パヤパ
Chul chul chul payapa
ドラマティックな序曲に汗ばむ
Sweating at the dramatic overture
デジャヴ 見つめ続けたくて
Déjà vu, I want to keep staring at it
カラフルなストーリー 心深く刻み込む
Engrave the colorful story deep in your heart
小さな闇が訪れても
Even if a small darkness visits
恋の呪文 唱えたなら
If you chant a love spell
きっと果てない空
Surely, from the endless sky
星屑のシャワー降り注ぐ
A shower of stardust will pour down
だから HAPPY STATION 目指して行こう
So let's aim for HAPPY STATION
50/50 合わせて
Combine 50/50
100%以上の愛
A love of more than 100%
ゆるぎなくここにあると
Is here, unwavering
私を思ってる
Thinking of me
チュル チュル チュル パヤパ
Chul chul chul payapa
chu-ru chu-ru chu-ru pa-ya-pa
君にありのまま 好きでいて欲しいと
I want you to love me just as I am
願いは 儚く 刹那の 魔法に
My wish is fleeting, caught in a momentary magic
MY DARLING もっと一緒に踊りましょう
MY DARLING, let's dance together more
SECRET NIGHT 素敵な
SECRET NIGHT, wonderful...
なぞり合うような デコレーション
A decoration that seems to trace each other
二人のハート 寄り添い合わせて
Bringing our two hearts close together
MY DARLING ねえ ビビッドな恋しましょう
MY DARLING, hey, let's have a vivid love
はじける SEXY BEAUTY
Bursting SEXY BEAUTY
生まれ変わって甘い夢
Reborn into a sweet dream
そっと彩る MY LOVE ほら
Gently coloring my love, look
世界は変わる
The world is changing
chu-ru chu-ru chu-ru pa-ya-pa
Kiss me 愛してる
Kiss me Aishiteru
Lyrica, Musica: つんく
Lyrics, Music: Tsunku
燃え尽きるわ この恋全部
This love will burn out completely
どんな結末が来ようと 覚悟してる
I'm prepared for whatever end may come
余裕なんて ほとんど無い
I have almost no composure left
必死でしがみついてるだけ
I'm just desperately clinging on
あなたの目 優しく抱き寄せる腕
Your eyes, your arms gently pulling me close
全てが 全てが 初めてだもん I'm fallen as a star
Everything, everything is a first for me, I'm fallen like a star
Kiss me 離さないで
Kiss me, don't let me go
Kiss me 自然なままで
Kiss me, just as you are naturally
この不安も拭い取ってね
Please wipe away this anxiety too
ねえ ねえ ねえ ねえ...
Hey, hey, hey, hey...
Touch me その指先
Touch me with those fingertips
Touch me その眼差しで
Touch me with that gaze
この私を包み込んで
Envelop me
Please Please Please Please...
愛してる
I love you
蘇るわ 昨日のこと
The events of yesterday come flooding back
あんなに心が揺れたの 初めてだもん
It's the first time my heart has wavered so much
寂しすぎて 正直怖い
It's so lonely, honestly it's scary
二人でいれないこの時が
This time when we can't be together
雨の朝 暖かな部屋でコーヒー
A rainy morning, coffee in a warm room
大人のフリから 本当の大人になりそう
From pretending to be an adult, I feel like I'm becoming a real one
Kiss me 危険なほど
Kiss me, so much it's dangerous
Kiss me 甘い口づけ
Kiss me with a sweet kiss
この願いを全部叶えて
Grant all of these wishes of mine
ねえ ねえ ねえ ねえ...
Hey, hey, hey, hey...
Knock me その眼差しで
Knock me with that gaze
Knock me 窓を叩いて
Knock me, knock on the window
この私を安心させて
Please put me at ease
Please Please Please Please...
愛してる
I love you
Kiss me
いけないほど
To an extent I shouldn't
Kiss me
甘いくちづけ
A sweet kiss
こんな願いを全部叶えて ねえ ねえ ねえ...
Grant all these wishes, hey, hey, hey...
Knock me
その魂で
With that soul of yours
Knock me
窓を叩いて
Knock on the window
こんな私を安心させて Please Please Please...
Make me feel at ease, please, please, please...
愛してる
I love you
Happy!
Are you ready?
One, two, jump!
Please enjoy Triangle Dreamer!
Day by day 日々に日々に 募るの片想い
Day by day, day by day, my unrequited love grows
同じクラスなのに 目眩の遠い人
Even though we're in the same class, he feels so dizzyingly far
カッコよくはない だけど優しい いつも頼れる彼
He's not cool, but he's kind, a guy I can always count on
放課後 下校途中の帰り道
On the way home after school
何だって話せる 親友の女の子
My best friend, a girl I can talk to about anything
スポーツ万能 勉強もできて 女子力 MAXです
Great at sports, smart in school, her girl power is at its max
どこにでもある よくあること
It's something you see anywhere, a common occurrence
急に彼女が
Suddenly, she says...
「あのね、実は私、好きな人がいるの」
“Um, actually, there's someone I like.”
「ちょ、マジで！？」
“Wait, seriously!?”
三角形 三角形の恋はきまぐれ
Triangle, a triangle love is fickle
一瞬で 一瞬で崩れるバランス
In an instant, the balance breaks in a single moment
ベタな漫画みたいなフラグ
A cliché flag just like in a manga
まさかね 自分が立てちゃうなんて
I can't believe I'm the one setting it off
残念すぎます！
This is so unfortunate!
三角形 三角形の恋は不安定
Triangle, a triangle love is unstable
なんちゃって
Just kidding...
なんちゃってじゃ済まないカテゴリー
It's a category where “just kidding” won't cut it
恋と友情 ゆらゆらめいて
Love and friendship, wavering back and forth
なんか青春しちゃいます
It feels like a youth drama
わたし 困っちゃいます
I'm at a loss
完敗です お似合いすぎるわ 勝てっこない
A complete defeat, you two look too good together, I can't win
悔しいけど どこかそんなんじゃなくて本心
It's frustrating, but somehow it's not like that, it's my true heart
っていうか既に 応援モード
Actually, I'm already in cheering mode
むしろ 清々しい
In fact, it's quite refreshing
だけど彼女は不思議な顔
But she has a strange look on her face
真剣な目で
With serious eyes...
「そうじゃなくて私、あなたが好き、ごめん」って
She says, “That's not it, I like you, sorry.”
「え、マジで！？」
“Eh, seriously!?”
三角形 三角形の恋はきまぐれ
Triangle, a triangle love is fickle
一瞬で 一瞬で崩れるバランス
In an instant, the balance breaks in a single moment
わたし
Me
アナタ
You
彼女とわたし
Her and me
超絶！複雑！百合展開は想定外です！
Transcendent! Complex! This girls' love development is unexpected!
三角形 三角形の恋は不安定
Triangle, a triangle love is unstable
なんちゃって
Just kidding...
なんちゃってじゃ済まないカテゴリー
It's a category where “just kidding” won't cut it
解けないパズル 与えたもうた
An unsolvable puzzle given to us
神よ 恨んじゃいます
Oh God, I resent you for this
わたし
I...
悩んじゃいます
...am worrying!
あー、もうすごいヤバい！
Ah, this is getting crazy!
好きだよ、好きだけど、
I like you, I do like you,
ってそういう意味じゃなくって！
but I don't mean it in that way!
だって女の子同士だし！
I mean, we're both girls!
ねぇ神様、どうしたらいいの？
Hey God, what should I do?
わたし、どうしたいの？
What do I want to do?
HELP ME!
なんか変だ 合いも故郷も
Something's strange. Love, hometown,
年も性別も関係ない
age, and gender don't matter.
けど けど けど...
But, but, but...
三角形 三角形の恋は
Triangle, triangle love...
きまぐれ
...is fickle.
一瞬で 一瞬でくずれる
In an instant, in an instant,
バランス
the balance collapses.
普通の恋
Ordinary love...
普通の恋 夢みてたのに
I was dreaming of an ordinary love,
ノーマル設定のわたしじゃちょっと
but for me with normal settings,
無理ゲーすぎます
it's too much of an impossible game.
三角形 三角形の恋は
Triangle, triangle love...
不安定
...is unstable.
なんちゃって なんちゃってじゃ
"Just kidding" is a category...
済まないカテゴリー
...you can't just brush off.
彼女のこと
If I could come...
好きになれたなら
...to like her...
なんて妄想
...is the kind of delusion...
しちゃいます
...I'm having.
わたし
Something's...
どうかしてます
...wrong with me.
行くよー！
Here we go!
バウバウ！
Bau Bau!
Wow, Ruffians!
Ruffians!
Bau Bau! Thank you, Ruffians!
That was so much fun!
Yeah, you know, I got a bit dizzy though.
With the bubbles and changing so quickly!
Nice and fast!
Yeah, you know, up in the bubble there,
it was a little bit silly!
But did we surprise you?
And we got to see you as well, even more close up than usual!
Yeah! Wow, those last two songs we sang were...
"Kiss Me I'll Stayed" together with Okayu-senpai...
...and "Triangle Dreamer" with Okayu-senpai,
Mio-senpai, and Subaru-senpai!
What'd you think, Ruffians?
"Kiss Me I'll Stayed" is a song I've always wanted to sing together with Okayu-senpai!
Yeah, it's a little bit more sexy!
A bit of a sexy song, huh? Yeah!
And "Triangle Dreamer"!
Yeah, the best of idol songs!
The choreography was so cute!
Ruffians, are you still alive?
Alive?
Yeah! Bau Bau!
All of our senpai were so cute in person!
Bau Bau!
And getting to jump in the bubble!
Yeah! It was a blast!
A lot of firsts this year, right?
Yeah! Well, we have a tiny, tiny announcement.
You know, it's FUWAMOCO's birthday, right?
Our birthday!
And so, we have something we'd like to share with you!
Ready? Okay! Do-don-don!
Bau Bau!
It's time to celebrate both of our birthdays...
...with our FUWAMOCO 2026 Birthday Merch!
FUWAMOCOの生誕グッズ紹介、
FUWAMOCO's birthday merch introduction...
始まるよー！
...is starting!
First, we became fluffy and fuzzy idols with the...
...Fuwa Fuwa Idol Fuwawa and Moco Moco Idol Mococo acrylic stands!
Drawn by our mama, Icomochi-mama!
They're rather big compared to
regular acrylic stands, so we think
they'll be a great addition to your collection. Big size and cute!
Next, we have the silly Ehehe Angel and
Hoeh?! Devil rubber figurines!
We're now palm-sized figures perfect for
displaying on your desk. In our Halloween outfits!
This one is big!
We finally have FUWAMOCO plushies in our
out-and-about casual outfits!
But this time, we also speak when you hug us!
It's the Yappy Puppy FUWAMOCO Sounds Plushies!
おしゃべりぱぴー☆
Chatty Puppy☆
ぬいぐるみ の ふわもこ だよ！
I'm the plushie FUWAMOCO!
ぎゅっと すると
If you squeeze me tight,
いろいろ しゃべるよ！
I'll say all sorts of things!
どんな ボイス が 出るか お楽しみに！
Look forward to seeing what kind of voices come out!
We have the Fuwawa to GO☆Finger Puppet!
Whoa!
They both come with one extra Ruffian kigurumi costume you can dress up in and bring around with you everywhere!
ふわわ の 指パペット！
Fuwawa's finger puppet!
どこでも 一緒に 連れていける サイズ で 着せ替え ラフィアンズ 衣装 も あるよ！
It's a size you can take with you anywhere, and there's also a Ruffians costume to change into!
Finally, we have two different ASMR voice packs,
"Back from a Fluffy Date♡" with Fuwawa,
and "Sweet and Fuzzy Needy Puppy" from Mococo!
ASMRボイス は 英語 と 日本語 両方 で 収録 してます！
The ASMR voices are recorded in both English and Japanese!
They made our hearts beat so fast!
Be ready to blush when you take a listen to them! Ugh!
The merch is separated into two sets,
Fuwawa's Birthday Merch and Mococo's Birthday Merch!
If you purchase the full set, they come with bonuses,
including a cheki-style card with a special bonus voice!
グッズ は ふわわセット と もここセット に 分かれています！
The merch is split into a Fuwawa set and a Mococo set!
セット ごとに チェキ風カード と 特典ボイス が つきます！
Each set comes with a cheki-style card and a bonus voice!
The regular version will have a foil-stamped replica signature and message, so it'll be just as cute!
数量限定セット は 直筆サイン 入り だよ！
The limited edition set includes a hand-signed autograph!
We put lots of love into each and every signature, so we hope you look forward to it!
たくさん の 愛情 込めて サイン 書きますね！
We'll put lots of love into writing the signatures!
Please check out the Hololive Official Online Shop and look for the link in the description or comment area, okay?
ぜひ、ホロライブ 公式ショップ に チェック してください！
Please check the Hololive official shop!
Bau bau! What did you think, Ruffians? Our birthday merch is pretty cute, huh?
Well, the reservations will be going on sale right after the birthday live here ends! So don't forget, okay?
生誕 の グッズ の 予約 は この後 開始 しますので、お忘れなく チェック してくださいね！
Reservations for the birthday merch will start after this, so please don't forget to check them out!
You can use the link below or on the side here! Don't forget, okay?
We put a lot of love into it and Icomochi-mama too! Thank you Icomochi-mama! Right after this ends! Time to go go go! Okay! Go buy it!
Well, we performed more special collab songs with our dear senpais...
...but there's still one mystery guest we haven't met yet, right?
そう！ まだ 会ってない 謎のゲスト が 一人 いるんだよね！
That's right! There's still one mystery guest we haven't met yet!
Well, shall we give the Ruffians a hint?
Ruffians, are you curious? Bau bau!
Could it be...? Could it be...?
YAGOO-san? That's a good guess maybe!
But we'll see, huh?
Maybe you should get ready...
...because, you know, they aren't quite as bad as Pero, but they can get pretty nasty sometimes! Oh!
Mococo-chan, you shouldn't be rude to our next guest or anything, right?
Especially before calling them out!
We'll see!
Well, let's get them out here then!
Who could it be? Who could it be?
Okay! せーの！
Okay! One, two!
どうぞ！
Please come out!
わわわ！ きたしん や！ きたしん や！ きたしん や！
Wow wow wow! It's Kita-shinya! It's Kita-shinya! It's Kita-shinya!
ぱぴーきゅん！ いちゅーちゅー！
Puppy-kyun! Kissy kissy!
自己紹介 お願いします！
Please introduce yourself!
クロちゃん です！ わわわー！ しんやー！
I'm Kuro-chan! Wa-wa-wa! Shinya!
はじめまして！
Nice to meet you!
チワワ じゃないよ！ ふわわ だよ！
I'm not a Chihuahua! I'm Fuwawa!
ふわわ じゃないよ！ もここ だよ！
I'm not Fuwawa! I'm Mococo!
二人 合わせて、ふわもこ です！ バウバウ！
Together we are FUWAMOCO! Bau bau!
よろしく お願いします！
Nice to meet you!
ふわもこ の わちゃわちゃ バースデー フェスティバル に 来てくれて ありがとう ございます！
Thank you so much for coming to FUWAMOCO's Wacha Wacha Birthday Festival!
ハッピー バースデー だしん よ、ふわもこ！ いいしん ねー！
Happy birthday, FUWAMOCO! It's great!
ちょっと ね、えっと、視聴者 の ラフィアンズ は たくさん いると 思いました けど、クロちゃん が どんな 人 なのか 説明 してもらえます か？
Wait, um, I think there are many Ruffians watching, but could you explain what kind of person Kuro-chan is?
自分 で すん の？ それ。
I'm doing it myself?
Introduction!
分かった しん よ。だって これ 海外 の 人 も 見てます もんね？ 海外 の 人 も 分かる 自己紹介 します からね。
I understand. Since people from overseas are also watching, right? I'll do an introduction that people overseas will understand.
Nice to meet you, nice to meet you! Chu-chu-chu-chu-tulip!
Huh? Oh...
ねえ、止まらないで！ え、クロちゃん は、え、チューリップ？
Hey, don't stop! Uh, Kuro-chan is, uh, a tulip?
いや、チューリップ、ノー、ノー、ノー、ノー。
No, tulip, no, no, no, no.
ちょっと まだ 分からない かもしれない から。
They might not understand yet.
安田大サーカス という トリオ の 芸人さん で、豆柴の大群 の プロデューサー も やっていて 作詞 も している、クロちゃん です！
I'm a comedian in a trio called Yasuda Dai Circus, and I'm also the producer of MAMESHIBA NO TAIGUN, and I also write lyrics. I'm Kuro-chan!
バウバウ！ じゃあ、今回 は 英語 で お願いします！
Bau bau! Then, please do it in English this time!
In English!
僕 が？
Me?
Yeah!
自分 で？
By myself?
そんな こと 急に 言われたら、イッツ・シャイン！ パッ フラワー！
If you tell me that suddenly... It's shine! Pa! Flower!
もう言い訳は無し！
No more excuses!
ねえ聞いてる？人の話。ねえ。
Hey, are you listening? To what I'm saying. Hey.
頑張って！
Good luck!
えっと、何だろう、何だろう。えっと...
Um, what should I say, what should I say. Um...
Famous comedian!
おおー！
Ooh!
あと、Idol producer.
And, idol producer.
いやいやいや。
No, no, no.
やってるしんよ。
I'm doing it, shin!
あー、できるしん！
Ah, you can do it, shin!
いやいや、すごい！
No, no, that's amazing!
クロちゃんテレビでよく見てるけど...
I often see Kuro-chan on TV, but...
ちょっとフワモコのペットの、ペロちゃんと、えっと、ちょっと似てるところが、たくさんあるね。
You have a lot of similarities with FuwaMoco's pet, Pero-chan.
えっ、どこ？
Wait, where?
後ろの、彼を見てください。見えますか？
Look at him behind us. Can you see him?
そっくりですよ。ペロです。
He's just like you. It's Pero.
ちょっと待って。球体というか、丸いところが似てるだけじゃない？ねえ。
Hold on. Isn't it just the spherical... I mean, the roundness that's similar? Hey.
それじゃない！
That's not it!
本当？
Really?
えっと、クロちゃんと似てるところは...
Um, the parts that are similar to Kuro-chan are...
嘘つきで、女の子好きで、やらしくて...
Being a liar, liking girls, and being lecherous...
うん！
Yeah!
だからね、見た目で騙されないで。
So, don't be fooled by appearances.
クロちゃん、そんなんで大丈夫なの？言われて。
Kuro-chan, are you okay with being told that?
いや、ひどい。悲しくなってきた。えーん、えーん、えーん。
No, that's terrible. I'm getting sad. Waah, waah, waah.
エンポイポイフン！
En-poi-poi-fun!
ええー！？
Eeeh?!
全然人のギャグ聞かないよね、君たちは。
You guys don't listen to my jokes at all.
できれば、クロちゃんはペロの友達になってくれませんか？
If possible, would Kuro-chan like to be Pero's friend?
フワモコの友達じゃなくてペロの友達なの？
Pero's friend, not FuwaMoco's friend?
そう。フワモコはクロちゃんと友達になりたくないから。
Yeah. Because FuwaMoco doesn't want to be friends with Kuro-chan.
おかしくない、それ？
Isn't that weird?
いやいや、気持ち悪いから！
No, no, because it's gross!
いや、気持ち悪くない。マニアには受ける。
No, it's not gross. Maniacs love it.
違う。フワ、気持ち悪い、やっぱり。
No. Fuwa thinks it's gross, after all.
でも、モコちゃん、ちょっとやりすぎですよ。失礼です。
But, Moco-chan, that's going a bit too far. It's rude.
いや、もし、もし、ペロと仲良くなってほしいんだったら、フワモコちゃん、クロちゃんにかわいらしく頼んだほうがいいんじゃない？
Well, if you want me to get along with Pero, shouldn't FuwaMoco-chan ask Kuro-chan in a cute way?
はあ？
Huh?
NO!
えっ、NO？
Eh, NO?
NO!
しっかりとした否定。
A very firm denial.
えっ、まあ、けど、ペロ可愛いから仲良くなってもいいと思ってるよ。
Well, Pero is cute, so I think I'm okay with getting along.
あー、嬉しい！嬉しい嬉しい！
Ah, happy! Happy, happy!
可愛くないけど、なんか仲良くなってくれたら嬉しいかな？
He's not cute, but I'd be happy if you got along with him.
感情が、感情がいろいろありすぎるのよ、本当。
There are just too many emotions going on, really.
まあ、まあ。クロちゃんって芸人さんだけど、アイドルになりたいんですよね？
Well, well. Kuro-chan, you're a comedian, but you want to be an idol, right?
ねー。
Right?
そう。もともとアイドルになろうと思ったのに、騙されて芸人にさせられたから、アイドルは本当に夢。ドリーム。
Yeah. I originally wanted to be an idol, but I was tricked into being a comedian. So being an idol is truly my dream. My dream.
あー、悲しいね。かわいそう。
Ah, how sad. Poor thing.
でも、ドリームって大事ですから。
But dreams are important.
大事！
Important!
うん。
Yeah.
さあ、で、まあ、クロちゃんのドリームはアイドルなんだから...
So, since Kuro-chan's dream is to be an idol...
もうせっかく、一緒に歌ってくれませんか？
Since we're here, why don't you sing with us?
あ、いいしんよ、いいしんよ！オッケーだしんよ！歌って踊れるしんよ。
Ah, that's fine, shin! It's okay! I can sing and dance, shin!
え、何？
Eh, what?
うん、この曲、ドリームの曲ね。
Yeah, this song is a dream song.
あの、ハードル上げないで。
Um, don't raise the stakes too high.
えー、大丈夫ですよ。ねー。
Eh, it'll be fine. Right?
アイドルのプロデュースもやってるし。
You also produce idols.
そうそう、実力見せてよ！
Yeah, show us your talent!
見せて！
Show us!
オッケーだしんよ。行くしんよ、行くしんよ。
It's okay, shin. Here I go, here I go, shin.
オッケー！うん！
Okay! Yeah!
じゃあ、すごく可愛い曲を一緒に歌いましょう！
Then, let's sing a very cute song together!
えっ、何だろう。楽しみ。
Eh, I wonder what it is. I'm excited.
オッケー。はーい。
Okay. Here we go.
じゃあ、一緒にタイトルコールしましょうね。
Then, let's do the title call together.
うん。
Yeah.
せーの！
One, two!
ちゅ、多様性。
Chu, Tayousei.
あ、多様性やるの？
Ah, we're doing Tayousei?
ちゅ、多様性。
Chu, Tayousei.
我愛你　酔いが醒めない
I love you, the intoxication won't fade.
Oh, I need you　恋が醒めない
Oh, I need you, the love won't fade.
お生憎様の慣れ果て　唆して
A pitiful shadow of myself, entice me.
無問題　破滅してみて
No problem, try being ruined.
Hold me tight　トラウマの味
Hold me tight, the taste of trauma.
猛反対　お手お座りでハイ❤報酬
Strong opposition, give a hand, sit, and "here's your reward❤"
喉の奥がジンジンジン
The back of my throat is tingling.
僕はドクンドクン
My heart is thumping.
鼓動で孤独消してみせてよ
Try erasing the loneliness with the heartbeat.
愛も恋も度外視して
Disregarding both love and romance.
僕を独占して
Monopolize me.
このまま中毒になるまでチューしよう
Let's keep kissing until we're addicted.
Get get get on!
Get get get on chu!
熱く　とろけるくらいに溢れた気持ちが
Feelings overflowing enough to melt with heat.
たまらないでしょ
It's irresistible, right?
Get get get on chu!
我愛你　無問題
I love you, no problem.
Get get get on chu!
ポン・チー・カン　勝負はいつも
Pon, Chii, Kan, the match is always...
トンチンカン　僕に言わせて
Absurd, let me say it.
ちんぷんかんぷんだ　最後はロンでしょ？
It's all Greek to me, the end is "Ron", right?
もう何回？　殺られればいい
How many more times? How many times should I be killed?
Oh, one night 忘れられない
Oh, one night, I can't forget.
終わんないトキメキ偏愛♡予習
Never-ending heart-throbbing partiality ♡ preview
喉の奥がチクンチクン
A prickling sensation in the back of my throat
僕はドクンドクン
My heart is thumping
心臓ごと 引きずり出して見せてよ
Drag it all out, even my heart, and show me
ってよ
...so they say.
気持ちいい めんどくさいけど
It feels good, though it's a pain
やっぱ照れくさいけど
And it's embarrassing after all
死ぬまで忘れられないチューしよ
Let's share a kiss we'll never forget until we die
いかれた街はゾンビで溢れる
This crazy town is overflowing with zombies
君は僕に恋してる
You're in love with me
ときめく胸に繋がる導火線を引きなよ
Pull the fuse that connects to your throbbing chest
いくよ Bet bet bet on chu!
Here we go, bet bet bet on chu!
Bet on chu!
Bet bet bet on chu!
本気で狂えるくらいの愛おしさが
A love so intense it could drive you mad
美しいでしょ
Is beautiful, isn't it?
Get get get on chu!
Get on chu!
せーの
Ready, go!
ポン・チー・カン
Pon! Chi! Kan!
終わんない
It won't end!
Get Get Get on chu!
我爱你 無問題
Wǒ ài nǐ, no problem!
Get Get Get on chu!
やったー！やったー！うまくいったしんよー！
Yay! Yay! We did it-shin!
ありがとうー！よかったー！
Thank you! I'm so glad!
頑張ったね、クロちゃん！楽しかったー！ありがとうー！
You did your best, Kuro-chan! It was fun! Thank you!
ありがとう！ Thank you!
Thank you! Thank you!
え、ちょっとね、さよならする前に...
Actually, before we say goodbye...
お、何？
Oh, what is it?
えっと、1個お願いしてもいいですか？
Um, could we ask you one favor?
1個だけだしんよー
Just one thing-shin!
あー、1個だけじゃん！
Aw, just one thing!
えっと、FUWAMOCOは魔界の番犬で、Bau Bauをよく言ってるんですけど...
Well, FUWAMOCO are guard dogs of the Underworld, and we often say 'Bau Bau'...
クロちゃん、カメラに向かってFUWAMOCOのように可愛いBau Bauをしてもらえますか？
Kuro-chan, could you do a cute 'Bau Bau' for the camera like FUWAMOCO does?
えー！できるかなぁ？
Eh! I wonder if I can do it?
ほっ、ほっ！
Ho, ho!
いくしんよ！
Here I go-shin!
Bau Bau!
へ？バウバウ...それがベスト？
Huh? Bau Bau... is that your best?
えー、もう一回！もっとやって！
No, one more time! Give it more!
はい、はい。んん〜
Okay, okay. Mmm~
Bau Bau!
可愛いかな？
Was that cute?
えっと、実はもう一個やりたいことがあるんですけど...
Um, actually, there's one more thing I want to do...
何？
What is it?
さっきもやりましたけど、FUWAMOCOはいつもやってる自己紹介があって...
Like we did earlier, FUWAMOCO has a self-introduction we always do...
できれば3人で一緒にやりたいです！
And if possible, I'd like to do it with all three of us!
あ、あれ可愛かったからやりたいクロちゃんも！
Ah, that was cute, Kuro-chan wants to do it too!
じゃあ行きますよー！ OK!
Then here we go! OK!
チワワじゃないよ、フワワだよ！
Not a Chihuahua, I'm Fuwawa!
フワワじゃないよ、クロちゃんだよ！
Not Fuwawa, I'm Kuro-chan!
へ、クロちゃんじゃないよ、モココだよ！
Eh, not Kuro-chan, I'm Mococo!
3人合わせて、FUWA... あ、いやいや...
And together we are FUWA... ah, wait, wait...
アイヤイヤー！何で？怒んないで！どうしたの？
Aieee! Why? Don't be mad! What's wrong?
ぜんぜんクロちゃん出てこないから何なのそれ！
Kuro-chan isn't supposed to be in it at all, what's with that!
おい、もう嘘とかつくないよね！ 嘘じゃないよ...
Hey, stop telling lies already! It's not a lie...
おい、一歩前！
Hey, step forward!
モココ・パーンチ！
Mococo Punch!
痛い！あたたたた... あたたたた...
Ow! Ouch ouch ouch... ouch ouch ouch...
救急車1台！
Call an ambulance!
いらないよ！もう嘘！
We don't need one! Stop lying!
嘘じゃないってばー！Bau Bau! 何でBau Bau怒んのちょっと！
I'm telling you, it's not a lie! Bau Bau! Why are you mad at Bau Bau?!
落ち着いて、落ち着いて... 何でー...
Calm down, calm down... But why...
大丈夫、モコちゃん、大丈夫。
It's okay, Moco-chan, it's okay.
じゃあ、クロちゃんはこれからもみんなをいっぱい笑顔にして、素敵なアイドルになってくださいね！
Well, Kuro-chan, please keep making everyone smile and become a wonderful idol!
だしんよー！
I will-shin!
Bau Bau!
じゃあモコちゃん、最後にクロちゃんにハイタッチしてお別れしようね！ オッケー！
Then Moco-chan, let's give Kuro-chan a high-five and say goodbye! Okay!
仲直り、仲直り... 仲直りだしん？
Make up, make up... We're making up-shin?
オッケーだしんよ、ハイタッチ！
It's okay-shin, high-five!
ほら、ほら、ほら...
Come on, come on, come on...
バッ！ あーっ！ちょっとー！
Bwah! Ah! Wait a minute!
ひどくないもー、ちょっと、何なのー。
That's mean! Hey, what was that for?!
けど、FUWAMOCOちゃん、本当にお誕生日おめでとうございまーす！
But FUWAMOCO-chan, a very happy birthday to you!
ありがとうー！ おめでとうだしんよ！
Thank you! Congratulations-shin!
Bau Bau! ギュンからのバッギュン！おめでとうハート！
Bau Bau! From a Kyun to a Bakkyun! Happy birthday heart!
Bau Bau!
S-Stay tuned!
Fireworks! Beautiful fireworks! Yeah!
たまやー！かぎやー！Bau Bau!
Tamaya-! Kagaya-! Bau Bau!
Wow! That was so high!
Things kind of got really crazy, I'm not too sure what happened.
クロちゃんすごすぎて、わからなくなってきたかも...
Kuro-chan was so intense, I might have lost track of things...
But we still have one more thing, one more very exciting thing to share with you!
まだまだ楽しみがあるよ！
There's still more to look forward to!
Wow... maybe Ruffians, can you guess what it is?
何かな？何かな？
What could it be? What could it be?
Wow... FUWAMOCO and our 1st anniversary...
And at last we were able to release
our first original song, "Bring It On!"
And then for our second anniversary, we were
able to release "Lifetime Showtime!"
Our original song that's grown with us
along this journey, a very special song.
And you know, for FUWAMOCO, singing and
dancing is something that means so much to us!
Yeah, music!
And Ruffians, you might have heard that
you'd like to hear more from us too, right?
Yeah! Yeah! What do you think? Yeah!
Well... our announcement is...
Drumroll! Okay, drumroll please!
Bau bau bau bau bau...
DA-DAN! A new original song!
Yeah! 新しいオリ曲！
Yeah! A new original song!
And this song is extra special!
It's written by none other than the legendary
rock idol song composer Matsukuma Kenta-san,
who's worked with many famous idol groups
so we love, also writing music for the
idol group that Kuro-chan produces,
MAMESHIBA NO TAIGUN!
But Ruffians, you might be
a little bit surprised, okay?
So get ready!
Ruffians, with this song, we'd like to express
our deepest feelings as demon dogs.
DEMON'S RESIDENCE.
「相棒、どこへ行こうか」
"Partner, where shall we go?"
ネオンの脇を抜け
Slipping past the neon lights
バブルガムがはじけたら
Once the bubblegum pops
let's go
最低な夜を潜って
Diving through the lowest of nights
僕らは群れをなす
We form a pack
「あの頃よりもマシだね」
"It's better than back then, isn't it?"
my way
「不完全なんです」
"It's incomplete"
首輪をつけた
Wearing a collar
良い子なんかんじゃもう
If it's just about being a good girl, then
イ　ヤ
NO WAY
Ah!!
DEMON'S RESIDENCE
噛みついていけ
Bite your way through
この街は檻のようで
This city is like a cage
気分はどうだい
How are you feeling?
泣いているのかい
Are you crying?
鎖をちぎって
Tear off the chains
叫んでいたいんだ
I want to keep shouting
stray dogs
彼方へと
To the beyond
飛ぶ鳥を
At the flying birds
見上げるだけかい
Are you just looking up?
それでいいのかい
Is that really okay?
震えるなら
If you're trembling
ほら青く
Look, turn blue
「説教なんかはいらない」
"I don't need any preaching"
スプレー缶振って
Shaking the spray can
イタズラ書きで
With graffiti
彩る runway
Color the runway
愛情なんか coin toss
Affection is just a coin toss
誰に bet するのか
Who are you betting on?
不確定要素ばかりね
It's nothing but uncertainties
lonely
二人で
The two of us
ひとつと決めた
Decided to be as one
あの日を忘れない
I won't forget that day
Ah!!
DEMON'S RESIDENCE
満天の空
A star-filled sky
あの星がひどく不快で
Those stars are terribly unpleasant
勝利はどうだい
How's victory?
味がするのかい
Does it have a taste?
鎖を噛んで
Biting the chains
唸っていたいんだ
I want to keep growling
stray dogs
僕ら宇宙さえも
Even the universe
撃ち落として
We'll shoot it down
見下ろす奈落
Looking down into the abyss
ビルは輝く
Buildings are shining
LOL Now I am
free!!
Woah oh oh oh oh oh...
孤独を分け合い食べた
We shared and ate our loneliness
あの日を忘れない
I won't forget that day
嗚呼
Ah
夜を睨んだ stray dogs
The stray dogs that glared at the night
そうだ怪物は世界のほうさ
That's right, the monster is the world itself
抜け出せるのかい
Can you break out?
足は動くかい
Can your legs move?
走るなら今
If you're going to run, it's now
DEMON'S RESIDENCE
stray dogs 僕ら
We stray dogs
この街を駆け抜けていけ
Let's run through this city
地獄の果てに
At the end of hell
何が見えるかい
What can you see?
鎖をちぎって
Tear off the chains
叫んでいたいんだ
I want to keep shouting
stray dogs 僕ら
We stray dogs
この街は檻のようで
This city is like a cage
君ならどうだい
How about you?
共に駆けるかい？
Will you run together?
夜明けが合図だ
Dawn is the signal
行こう
Let's go
アンコール！
Encore!
side by side
Lyrics: Kris Roche / Music: Alobahn (-81), Kris Roche / Arrangement: Alobahn (-81)
Bau bau! Thank you for always being here for FuwaMoco!
Please listen to:
side by side!
Finally we made it through but not without some tears
With the help of friends so true we faced all of our fears
Now we're here to celebrate all that we have done
I can feel it's more than just a game of fate
'cause our stories have just begun
Hand in hand we're not waiting on tomorrow
From now on its the heart that we will follow
We'll move on passed the heartbreak and the sorrow If you stay by my side
Dancing harmonics feeling the music
as we come alive, and sparks ignite
We're making memories everyday underneath
the summer sky and through the night
We're singing melodies every time we hear music
from inside as hearts collide
Bringing out the best in each other now
we're feeling free like were meant to be
Even though there's been rough times when nobody wanted us,
we kept going and we kept dreaming!
Now we're here, we're not alone anymore!
We'll be here together, with a smile to protect!
Come on, let's go!
Dancing harmonics feeling the music
as we come alive, and sparks ignite
We're making memories everyday underneath
the summer sky and through the night
We're singing melodies every time we hear music
from inside as hearts collide
Bringing out the best in each other now
we're feeling free like were meant to be
Nya nya nya nya nya nya nya...
Bau bau!
Thank you for the encore, Ruffians!
That was: side by side! Bau bau!
We're really happy we could perform side by side for the first time live today!
Yeah! 初披露できてとっても嬉しいです！
Yeah! We're so happy to perform it for the first time!
Side by side is a song made by Alobahn-san, but also between FuwaMoco!
Yeah, it's ours! We know it's a song that you love a lot,
but we also do because it's very special to us
since it's the ending theme for a visual novel that we care about!
NEKOPARA!
And with this song, our dream of seeing the opening or ending theme for a visual novel came true!
Yeah! そう、この曲でFUWAMOCOの夢、美少女ゲームの主題歌を歌うことが叶いました！
Yeah! That's right, with this song, FUWAMOCO's dream of singing a theme song for a bishoujo game came true!
Our dream came true! Thank you! ありがとう！
Our dream came true! Thank you! Thank you!
And thank you so much for joining us for our special day again this year!
It's been a dream with you!
And you know, it's all because of you that we're able to be here
and do all the amazing things that we do, so thank you!
Ah, this next song is our last song.
But, like, overall, it's a very special one.
You know, FUWAMOCO is Demon Guard Dogs.
We're here to protect your smile, right?
We'll continue to do that.
Protect your smile. Yeah, do our best, idol!
And just as our fluffy and fuzzy selves, too.
We'll continue to be here for thousands and thousands of demon dog years.
Always remembering that, you know, every day isn't given.
Yeah, we don't take anything for granted.
And you know, when you're down, we hope that you'll remember...
...that we're always here cheering you on, okay?
We'll cheer you on Ruffians!
So please listen closely to the lyrics of our last song for today.
明日も
Tomorrow
明後日も
The day after tomorrow
あなたが笑ってますように
I hope you'll be smiling
ずっと
Always
Lala...
Thank you so much Ruffians for spending our birthday with us today!
Please think of this song whenever things are rough and know Double B is here.
This last song is for you. Wishful Garnet!
過去を振り返ると
When I look back
思い出す ガーネットの空
I remember the garnet sky
あふれてく 光
Overflowing light
この瞳に映し出されたあの日は
That day reflected in these eyes
美しく 揺れる
Beautifully swaying
What do you think?
紅く 滲んだ空に
In the crimson-stained sky
願いました
I made a wish
どうかこの願い
Please let this wish
届けてください
Reach you
明日も
Tomorrow
明後日も
The day after tomorrow
あなたが笑ってますように
I hope you'll be smiling
離れ離れになっても
Even if we're apart
前を向けますように
I hope you can look forward
あなたを縛る鎖を
The chains that bind you
わたしが壊してあげる もう
I'll break them for you, no more
負けないで 進むこと
Don't lose, keep moving forward
いつでもそばにいるから
Because I'm always by your side
落ち込んだり
Being depressed
自信を無くした時だって
Or even when you lose confidence
目の前にいてくれる
You are there in front of my eyes
あなたの笑顔に 何度となく
To your smile, countless times
救われた
I was saved
だから
That's why
So I love you
挫けそうになったら 手を伸ばして
If you're about to give up, reach out your hand
まだ知らない 明日
To the tomorrow we don't know yet
一緒に見つけよう
Let's find it together
明日も
Tomorrow
明後日も
The day after tomorrow
あなたを照らしていたい
I want to keep shining on you
泣きそうになった時は
When you're about to cry
こっち向いてほしい
I want you to look this way
世界でひとりぼっち
Alone in the world
そんな風に思わないで
Don't think like that
愛してくれる人はきっと
People who love you surely...
いつもあなたを想ってる
...are always thinking of you
Wishful Garnet!
Lala...
願いました
I made a wish
どうかこの願い
Please let this wish
届けてください
Reach you
明日も
Tomorrow
明後日も
The day after tomorrow
あなたが笑ってますように
I hope you'll be smiling
離れ離れになっても
Even if we're apart
前を向けますように
I hope you can look forward
あなたを縛る鎖を
The chains that bind you
わたしが壊してあげる もう
I'll break them for you, no more
負けないで 進むこと
Don't lose, keep moving forward
輝く空へ
To the shining sky
明日も
Tomorrow
明後日も あなたが笑ってますように
The day after tomorrow, I hope you'll be smiling
離れ離れになっても
Even if we are far apart,
前を向けますように
I hope we can keep looking forward
あなたを縛る鎖を
The chains that bind you,
わたしが壊してあげる wo-oh
I will break them for you, wo-oh
もう負けないで進むこと
Never lose again, and keep moving forward
いつでもそばに
Always by your side,
あなたのそばに
By your side,
わたしはいつもいるから
Because I'll always be here
La la la...
Yeah! Yeah!
Wo-oh... La la la...
Bau bau!
Thank you so much for viewing!
We'll see you soon at our encore live in membership, okay?
Bau bau!
SEE YOU AT OUR ENCORE LIVE IN MEMBERSHIP!
メンバーシップでアンコールライブを続けてるよー！
The encore live continues in our membership!